mybloggertricks.com 2018-04-19

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting **MyBloggerTricks.com**. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice to give you a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) in accordance with our website. 

**What information do we collect?**

When commenting on our site or subscribing, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter, fill out the comment form or enter information on our site using the contact form.

**How do we use your information?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience — your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs. 

  * To improve our site — we continually strive to improve our site offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you. 

  * To improve customer service — your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs. 

  * To send periodic emails — The email address you provide may be used to send you regular newsletter or to answer your questions.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We strictly protect the security of your personal information. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except as stated herein. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access.

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your username and password, so do not share these with others.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow). These cookies enable the site to recognize your browser and, if you have a registered account, associate it with your registered account.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our site, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our site. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Choice: Opt-In/Opt-Out**

We allow our visitors to unsubscribe so that they will not receive future emails or newsletter.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Our site, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. If this server is in the USA, and you are under the age of 13, per the requirements of COPPA ([Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Children)), do not use this site.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our site and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Problems or complaints with Provider’s Privacy Policy**

We value your comments and opinions. If you have questions, comments or a complaint about compliance with this privacy policy you may _[contact us](http://contact.mybloggertricks.com/)_ or visit our office: [STCnetwork](http://www.stcnetwork.org/)

*Last updated Jan 7, 2017.
